ezonlineclassifieds.com 2017-06-13

# Big City Advertising's Privacy Policy

****

******General**

At Big City Advertising (Owned by MGA Web Productions) we respect the privacy of our customers and we've created this privacy statement so that you have easy access to information about our privacy practices. In general, Big City Advertising does not collect, store, use or disclose personally identifying information except in very specific instances, such as, for example, when you enroll as an advertiser with us. Whenever we collect such information, you will have a choice regarding whether to provide it, how it will be used, and to whom it will be disclosed. The instances in which Big City Advertising does collect and use information are specifically described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Information we request, and how we use it**

In several areas of Big City Advertising we ask you to provide various information by filling out and submitting an online form. We ask for your name, address and contact information so we can process your order, and so we can contact you if we have a question about your order. We ask for credit card information so we can fulfill your order, and so we can provide this information to the company or companies who process your credit card payment. We do not share or sell your personal information, including email addresses. 

**Information we do not collect**

When you visit our site, we do not collect your name, email address or any other personal information unless you provide it to us. 

**How we use email**

After you complete any form on our site, you will receive an email confirmation of your submission. Occasionally, we will send a Big City Advertising Newsletter or email updates on sales and products, to listed subscribers who we think might be interested in learning about sales and special events at our site. Unsubscribe instructions are included in each edition of the newsletter/email so that you may unsubscribe at any time.

**Information we do not share with others  **

Big City Advertising does not share, sell or trade email addresses, information collected as part of a survey or specific details about you or your household. We do not contribute to or participate in shared or cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your personal information. We do not release credit card or financial information for use by other companies. For privacy purposes, all information relating to our customers is stored on a highly secure server, and all credit card information is stored offline in an encrypted format.
